AMRIT SHARMA () Featured

GoLang Developer / NodeJS Developer / ReactJS Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Requirement Analysis, GoLang, NodeJS, ReactJS, MongoDB, Git, ExpressJS, JIRA



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Jalan Technology Consulting Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science]

Current Location: Jaipur

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Requirement Analysis, GoLang, NodeJS, ReactJS, MongoDB, Git, ExpressJS, JIRA, GoLang, Developer, ReactJS Developer, NodeJS

Developer, MERN Stack, Fullstack Developer

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

Working as Backend Developer (NodeJS and GoLang) with 3 years of experience in Web applications and business logic development.

Experience in GoLang, GRPC, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MicroServices, MongoDB and ReactJS.

Working experience on minimum 4 projects in Web Applications.

Experience of working while following Scrum and Agile methodologies.

Experience in writing microservices in GoLang following best practices like Using Clean

Architecture, Protocol Buffers, Test Driven Development, Exception Handling etc.

Experience in migrating NodeJS microservices in GoLang .

Skillful programming experience in developing Publisher-Subscriber model, SMTP client and server, HTTP server, standard SSO protocols (SAML, JWT, OAuth 2.0, OIDC,

WSFed), REST APIs etc.

Work Experience

Jalan Technology Consulting as Software Engineer Dec 2020 to Till Date

LoginRadius as Software Engineer Aug 2019 to Nov 2020

Jaipur Scientific Agriculture Solution (All On Block Corporation) as Software Engineer Dec 2017 to Jul 2019

Education

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience		
Golang	1.12	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
React.Js / ReactJS	16.14.0	2020	0 Year(s) 3 Month(s)		
Mongodb	4.2	2019	1 Year(s) 6 Month(s)		
Visual Studio Code	1.51	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
JIRA		2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
GIN	1.6.3	2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
Express / Express.js / ExpressJS	4.17.1	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
GIT	2.29.2	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
Gorrilla		2020	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		
Node.Js / NodeJS	14.15.1	2020	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time